So... how is he doing?
Citizen registration number 021723,
former chairman of the Citizen Health Bureau, Daedalus Yumeno.
He was stripped of authority by
order of the Administration Bureau.
Following his dismissal,
he has not done anything out of the ordinary.
Things are quiet.
Do you understand the reason for that, Kristeva?
You're in a good mood today.
Is that so?
It's just that I've accepted myself for who I am,
and I'm rising to heights where I've no need for others.
The monster no longer interests me...
But he's different.
His beloved Re-l Mayer,
granddaughter of the Administrator, has died...
along with that PROXY called Monad,
whose existence he had been concealing.
He has lost his raison d'être.
"The reason for existence", sir?
Look at the minimalist beauty of this world.
All of us are manufactured cogwheels in this utopia.
Our existence is allowed so we can
fulfill this "reason" we've been given.
But Daedalus Yumeno has lost both PROXY and Re-l Mayer,
his raisons d'être, at the same time.
In other words, he is a chipped cog.
Re-l...
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
A being that was sealed away, said
to be invincible and immortal, has died.
Do you know the reason why?
Its awakening will call forth destruction.
Blood will continue to be shed in our tranquil utopia.
Do you know the reason why?
The report has already been submitted.
There are many issues that we must address.
The weakening of both the magnetic field of the dome's outer shell
and the life support unit's energy source pose risks
that necessitate a drastic reform of
the entire system - now an imperative task.
That is one of the conclusions you have come up with.
Too much thinking will burden your mind and cause sin.
Meaning what happened to Re-l Mayer could have happened to you.
You know the reason why, do you not, Raul?
You are dismissed.
We must think about what we
must do now that we have lost PROXY.
We know too little.
And therefore must think.
Indeed.
Indeed...
Tell me the truth...
"I think, therefore I am"...
Chief,
you are hurt.
Visible wounds are nothing.
Just in case,
I will call for a medical check from the Health Bureau.
The Administrator won't give any answers.
He just poses questions.
Why is that?
I cannot understand why.
I can.
The grief-stricken cry of one who
has lost his most beloved in an instant...
Administrator, why do you avert your eyes?!
Why...
Why?!
The reality which is called Romdeau...
What is going on?!
Emergency stop code detected.
Emergency phase sequence initiated.
Confirmed.
meditation    existence
After a disconnection lasting two and a half minutes,
it automatically recovered.
We have not determined its cause,
but there has been no damage to the life
support or other systems due to this blackout.
"This blackout"?
Three weeks ago,
there were other blackouts with identical circumstances.
Were we informed of these?
No.
Each blackout was intermittent,
on the order of several milliseconds.
They were deemed accidents.
Analysis of the results indicating
intentional sabotage have been inconclusive.
A terrorist act by infected autoreivs...
no, by immigrants?
Still...
Two minutes and 17 seconds...
Kristeva.
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
Regarding the incidents that led to the most recent blackout,
from their times and results,
it can be conjectured that they were
experiments intended to fool the Security Bureau.
Beautiful.
What about this blackout?
I believe it is reasonable to construe it as a warning.
I see...
And the real reason for that is?
If we wish to keep the city's life support system operational,
a blackout must not exceed three minutes.
So the perpetrator does not wish to cause human deaths?
Indeed.
Actually...
please make an appointment for a medical check after all.
Let's ask him to do the examination.
However, his authority has been...
I'd like to ask you to do something for me as well.
Please find the research data he has hidden.
I don't intend to examine anyone anymore.
You may look like a boy, but you are a pretty brash man.
Could you please leave?
No, perhaps you are a romantic.
Deleuze will arrange for a different doctor.
Well...
what are you trying to say?
What are you talking about?
You called me all the way out here, yet...
I'm sorry Chief.
I no longer have...
anything to say.
The reason why I was manufactured
was to protect both her and the subject
and to raise her into a healthy girl.
But now that I've lost both of them,
I...
have lost my raison d'être.
As someone who heard your heart's cry of anguish,
I decided to come to do what I can.
You fancy yourself a telepath?
It's your fault.
For some reason, it only seems to
have an effect on Daedalus Yumeno...
strangely enough.
He says he agrees to examine me.
In the meantime, search for the data I asked you about earlier.
Where are you going, sir?
He needs a change of pace.
There's no need to worry.
However, he has not received permission to go outside yet.
Giving permission is my job, is it not?
Understood.
You are a cruel man.
There is no such "data" here.
I'll keep looking until I find it.
I'm competent.
So, you have lots of free time then.
They're fine.
They don't "socialize" with the Representative.
"The Representative"?
Oh, the Administrator.
Well, well...
you're quite thorough.
That is why you forced a laid off physician to do an examination.
Am I right?
Impressive.
You were faster than I thought.
You played around too much.
You're rather timid.
I know the limit for the life support system well enough.
It seems the Administrator has interpreted it as a warning.
That's a nice, misleading interpretation.
The Security Bureau will handle the rest by
arresting a convenient suspect at a convenient time.
Daedalus Yumeno, citizen registration number 021723.
Two minutes, 17 seconds and 23 milliseconds.
I did many tests, after all.
Was that a threat?
A very effective one.
Perhaps you thought I'd let out that you
got rid of someone who was in your way.
What are you talking about?
Using cogito was a bad idea.
Let's drop the pretense.
The only reason I took such a roundabout approach
was so we could talk without the Administrator eavesdropping.
Are you going to get rid of me in the same way?
Is it not enough that you took away my beloved and demoted me?
You brought it on yourself.
You used Monad as bait,
blinded the Administrator,
and concealed its existence.
I see.
You had something you had to hide from the Administrator
even after getting cornered with no way out.
It was another PROXY.
That incident was convenient;
you had hit a wall and needed to hide the
other PROXY's existence from the collective.
That's true.
And it erased the existence of yet another.
In other words...
Re-l Mayer is alive.
Are you all right, Re-l?
Yeah...
Did you find anyone?
Well,
I thought investigating the power plant was our first priority, so...
Now that we've gone outside, supplies are our top priority, right?
Iggy...
Don't worry, Re-l.
The city's retro, but its science is pretty good.
Its energy source matched the ship's.
As long as I connect them just
right, I should be able to interface-
Iggy.
There is no one in this city.
The outside world, hm?
You were able to deceive the Administrator.
But the eventual fate of those who leave utopia is clear...
What prompted a realist like her to risk her life
was her raison d'être...
It was PROXY itself.
You must have been thinking of
using her to obtain the other PROXY.
But you began to think that it would be impossible...
and that you would also lose her.
You cannot protect her if she's outside.
That is why you sent me the message.
You're saying I will cooperate with you?
You, who tried to murder Re-l?
I tried to murder her?
It can't be...
Maybe it'd be better if people didn't exist.
They will continue to work
until the world rots away.
For whom, though?
They've lost what was supposed to be their raison d'être - people.
They had no reason in the first place...
Re-l...
Well,
I was wondering what you'd do if I were to go away.
Don't jinx yourself.
What about you, Re-l?
What if I were to go away?
Silly.
I'd never leave you, Re-l.
It's not a laughing matter.
You're "laughing" though.
Hey, Re-l...
Don't worry.
I was just letting my weakness show for a bit.
Even you are a bit tired, huh.
I'll refuel the machine, so rest, okay?
As for myself...
For what have I been...
It's supposed to have been a journey to gain answers!
But...
even if I find PROXY...
I will...
Why would the Representative do that?
You're still young, after all.
It seems you've underestimated the Administrator.
Even if she is his grandchild, betrayal will lead to condemnation.
As a citizen, it's a rule that he should obviously follow.
And you thought you had him wrapped around your finger?
Let me ask you again what the
significance behind the blackout was.
That was a messa-
I am not such an optimist that I'll take things at face value.
I can easily tell that it's a poisoned dish.
By causing this blackout, you
obtained an enormous amount of energy.
What did you do with it?
I tried to revive PROXY.
Beautiful...
Submit to my terms.
I can give you a toy.
Of course, you don't have any other choice right now.
A "toy", huh.
Where'd you come from?!
Pretty pendant...
This is...
Something you treasure?
Not exactly...
Then gimme.
Hey!
Wait!
Why did PROXY die?
Because its amrita cells, which are
supposed to be immortal, were destroyed.
What caused that?
My "toy" was taken from me before I could investigate.
What I did to you was cruel.
As an apology, I'll lend you my toy.
You may play around with it however you wish.
However,
you must either be watched or directed
by an adult that knows right from wrong.
An adult's toy, huh.
Good boy.
Let's play forever!
That's not possible.
Why?
This is a very nice place.
That's true...
But...
I have someone I need to see.
Are you afraid?
Do you really not want to see him?
Even if you manage to see him,
you might be frozen in fear.
Maybe he can't change back anymore.
What you're looking for...
might be something cruel.
Do you still want it?
The truth...
He has it, so...
A charm...
I'll say this without fear of being misunderstood.
I want to save this world.
I'm so impressed that I'm close to tears.
It seems you lack training.
Unfortunately, I am not as soft as the Administrator.
If necessary,
I'll act as rudely as I like,
Daedalus Yumeno...
Now...
go ahead and work hard on your beloved research.
From now on, it's only for me.
Have you found it?
Not yet.
If you weren't able to find it,
it means it's not here.
What about Daedalus Yumeno's status?
I have reversed the dismissal.
From now on, he will carry out his
responsibilities under my direction.
It took a bit of work to tame him,
but he will learn much from this experience.
Only the victor has the right to become the righteous.
Welcome back.
I'm glad you've come back...
"For me"?
He doesn't even know the true significance.
It's all for you,
Re-l...
My Re-l...
Re-l!
Re-l.
Iggy...
Hey.
Pulling a disappearing act on me right off the bat?
I looked all over the place for you.
What?
What's the matter?
Hey...
Are you really all right?
It's nothing.
I had a dream.
There's no longer any need to sneak around.
So this is the product of two minutes and 17 seconds...
This should be more than enough.
Now...
all I have to do is load them.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
At the whitewashed ends of the earth,
a discarded past appears.
Those who have continued their journey beyond oblivion
meditation  in the white darkness
see the back of fate as it returns to intersect their path.